palermospizza.com 2014-04-17

# Privacy Policy | Palermo's Pizza | Palermo's Pizza

### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy identifies the type of information Palermo Villa, Inc., its affiliates and subsidiaries (collectively, "Palermo's") may collect from visitors of the Palermo's website (the "Website") and how Palermo's uses this information. If you have any questions about this policy, or the manner in which Palermo's uses personal information, we encourage you to contact us. Your use of the Website is also governed by the Terms & Conditions.

##### Use of Customer Information

Palermo's respects the privacy of its visitors and takes steps to prevent unauthorized disclosure of information to third parties. "Customer Information" includes any and all information received by Palermo's from visitors to the Website. Palermo's may store this information to evaluate its customers' preferences, send you coupons or other marketing materials, facilitate sweepstakes or other promotions or to improve the level of service to its customers. Palermo's will not disclose, share or sell any Customer Information to any other third party without your prior authorization except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.

##### Information Collected by Palermo's

The purpose of the Website is to collect information from customers and potential customers for certain products sold by Palermo's. Throughout the Website are forms that request information from you. These forms typically ask for contact information (such as name, mailing address, email address and phone number), information regarding your family and pizza preferences. The provision of such information by you is entirely voluntary. You may request that we delete any personal information we may have on file at any time by contacting Palermo's. In certain cases, Palermo's may disclose Customer Information to its vendors, such as purchasing and shipping information to vendors providing shipping services for its products to its customers.

##### IP Address Logging

Palermo's web servers collect domain names and/or IP addresses of users to measure what pages and features are accessed by its visitors. Palermo's uses software to collect and analyze this information. This information helps us administer the site, improve content and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. Palermo's may link IP addresses to personally identifiable information submitted to Palermo's. This information is used to verify whether a visitor has opted in to receiving additional information from Palermo's.

##### Cookies

Palermo's may use cookies or similar files or scripts throughout its website to enhance your convenience in using its Website, to improve search functionality or to hold information that you would otherwise need to re-key. Cookies are text files collected by a user's web browser. If you do not wish to accept cookies from its Website, you may configure your web browser so that it does not accept cookies; however, you may lose certain functions available on its Website.

##### Legal and Business Transfers

Palermo's reserves the right to disclose Customer Information satisfy (a) any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce applicable Terms of Use, including investigation of potential violations thereof and (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues. In the event of a merger or acquisition of all or part of Palermo's by another company, the acquirer would have access to the information maintained by Palermo's, which could include Customer Information.

##### Changes to Privacy Policy

In the future, Palermo's may offer new and different programs that necessitate a change in this Policy. Palermo's reserves the right to change its privacy policy at any time without prior notice. Any changes to the privacy policy will be posted on this page and will be effective immediately upon posting.

Governing Law and Jurisdiction This Policy, and Palermo's collection and use of Customer Information, shall be governed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the United States and the State of Wisconsin. Any disputes arising out of this Policy shall be adjudicated in a court of competent jurisdiction in the Eastern District of the State of Wisconsin.

##### Security

We are committed to preventing others from unauthorized access to the personal information you provide to us, and we maintain commercially reasonable procedures and technology designed for this purpose. This Website has reasonable technical and organizational security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under its control. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those security measures. Although we cannot guarantee that our systems are 100% secure 100% of the time, we periodically update and test our technology in order to improve the protection of Customer Information. We suggest that you install anti-virus software on your computer and routinely check for viruses, keyloggers, spyware and other programs that may become installed on your computer without your permission. If you believe that you have received a virus from Palermo's, please contact us as soon as possible so that we may take remedial measures to remove the virus.

Choice/Opt Out and Contact Information To request copies of or have Palermo's make changes or corrections to personal information in Palermo's possession please submit an online request to us by Contacting Us. You may also opt out of receiving further communications from us by submitting an online request or through either of the following methods:

##### Sending a request by mail to: 

Palermo's  
Attn: Customer Service  
3301 West Canal Street  
Milwaukee WI 53208  
(414) 571-7181

Effective Date: July 23rd, 2012
